So now we've finished the whole Uncial alphabet.
Again, it has just lower case, no capital letters.
And I think the best thing to do now, is to practice those letters.
Now sometimes when we are practicing we tend to say, "o.k., I'm going to make five As". Make your five As etc.
But it's not necessarily the best way to practice.
I'd like to think about putting the letters together with other letters that would be naturally occurring.
So we're going to make words.
And in practicing words, you practice how the letters fit together.
And you also practice a bigger assortment of letters.
Maybe we, we can't avoid the letters we don't like.
So a recommendation might be to write a whole string of letters, that one for each letter of the alphabet.
And practicing that way.
So that you keep your hand in good practice.